[{"answer": "350 meters... 400 meters..", "docId": "Event-Horizon.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I'm gone", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Captain my friend..", "docId": "Event-Horizon.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "We have a situation here..", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " No, he didn't", "docId": "Event-Horizon.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Saw what, Mr. my friend? What did you really see, because what you're describing is not physically possible..", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I don't know what happened to my friend", "docId": "Event-Horizon.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What you saw could have been an optical effect caused by gravitational distortion", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I'm telling you, I saw it..", "docId": "Event-Horizon.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " I know what I saw and it wasn't a fucking", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "\"Insane", "docId": "Event-Horizon.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "If it worked, yes", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "About an hour ago. In medical. I saw my son. He was lying on one of the examination tables and his legs were...", "docId": "Event-Horizon.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I've seen bodies before. This is different", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You've got to listen..", "docId": "Event-Horizon.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I didn't say that, I said the bi", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Maybe you're right. But it's still my command, and I have leeway to abort when I feel there is an unacceptable threat to my crew. And I think there is.  my friend, download all the files from the Event Horizon's computers. Coop, my friend, finish moving the CO2 scrubbers back onto the my friend", "docId": "Event-Horizon.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "It's done", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Get off the my friend now and wait for me at the airlock", "docId": "Event-Horizon.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Get out of there now", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You prep the gravity couches. I'm going to manually arm those explosives", "docId": "Event-Horizon.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It worked for my friend. Prep the tanks", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You're dead, I saw you die", "docId": "Event-Horizon.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Then who the fuck are you", "qsentId": 24}]